

CONTACT ME

- Avenida Peña Real 7, 28791, Soto del Real, Madrid, España
- alvaro.iglesias.diaz.13@gmail.com
- in Alvaro Iglesias Diaz

SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

Git version control

Web development with React.js and Redux

Team work using SCRUM Methodology

Knowledge on Docker, Lando and

API development with Node.js and

Advance Certificate on English (C1)

ÁLVARO IGLESIAS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Web developer specialized in React.js, with almost 3 years of experience with multiple languages and frameworks such as React.js, Laravel, Node.js and Express.js. I have experience working in a team, following the Agile SCRUM methodology and using Git and GitLab for version control. I am passionate about this industry and therefore I seek to learn new working techniques, that allow me to grow in this field, learning day by day and improving my skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web developer

Byron Group | April 2021 - July 2021

• Web application development using React.js and Redux

React.js developer

Digio Soluciones | February 2022- May 2022

- Web application development using Meteor.js and React.js
- I worked following SCRUM methodology and GitLab
- I participate on the creation of admin dashboards implementing Redux and custom hooks and refactoring multiple parts of the code in cleaner way.

EDUCATION

CEV. Centro de Estudios del Video

High National Degree on Multiplatform Applications Development | September 2019 - June 2021

- I studied web application development with HTML/CSS and JavaScript and creation of REST APIs with Laravel.
- Development of applications for Android and iOS

University of South Wales, UK

Bsc Hons Applied Computing | Septiembre 2021 - Mayo 2022

- I studied web programming with JavaScript, Oracle
 Databases, and GeoServer. I have developed Android
 applications in Kotlin and used PosgresQL to host maps on
 the server.
- My dissertation consisted on researching about delivery food services and how they affected traditional services.